https://www.dattapeetham.org/page/view/privacy-policy

Add Note
COVID-19 update: Datta Peetham will be closed for darshan till further notice
Collected Information and its use
We may collect information that can be used to identify you when you respond to certain inquiries or choose to use certain sections of our website. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone/mobile number, e-mail address, and, where appropriate, credit card number etc. However, we do not store sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card numbers. Also, when you visit our website, we or third-parties acting on our behalf will place a "cookie" - a text file containing a randomly assigned number on your computer - so that we have the ability to customize the look and feel of our website for you. Using embedded tracking technology, we or third-parties acting on our behalf will also collect a variety of other information regarding your usage of our website, including your IP address, your username, your session ID, the name of the browser you are using, information regarding web pages you view, and information regarding referring web pages, when you access our website.
While we or third-parties acting on our behalf use information about our users on an aggregated basis and will often share such data with unaffiliated third parties, this information, by its aggregate nature, contains none of your Personal Information. When we refer to an "unaffiliated" third party, we mean one that (i) is not controlled by us, (ii) does not control us, and (iii) is not controlled by the same party controlling us.
When We Disclose Your Personal Information
Except as explicitly stated in this privacy policy, we or third-parties acting on our behalf will not disclose to unaffiliated third parties any of your Personal Information without first obtaining your consent. We or third-parties acting on our behalf do and will continue to disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties in the following circumstances:
If required by law, regulatory or court order, or legal process;
If we believe that doing so would be in the public interest i.e., in cases where if we were to suspect that you were using our website in defiance to any law for the time being in force. The disclosure is always done with good faith in the interest of public at large.
After we or third-parties acting on our behalf disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties in such instances, we can no longer control the use or further disclosure of your Personal Information. Consequently, we or third-parties acting on our behalf will not be responsible to you for such use or further disclosure.
Security
We and third-parties acting on our behalf take precautions involving physical, electronic, and managerial controls to protect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, and alteration any of your Personal Information in our possession. We or third-parties acting on our behalf may employ industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer encryption when requesting certain financial Personal Information from you. We or third-parties acting on our behalf do not, however, use such encryption during your day-to-day use of our website. You should note that the confidentiality of any information transmitted over the Internet cannot be guaranteed.
Links to Other Sites
Please take note that this privacy policy applies only to our website. It does not apply to any other web or other sites to which a link may be provided as part of our website. We cannot control and/or are not responsible for the actions of third parties operating such sites. It shall not be assumed that the existence of an affiliation with or a link from, our website to any such other site to mean that it has a privacy policy similar to this one. You should review the privacy policy of any such site.
Avadhoota Datta Peetham © 2015 - 2020 All Rights Reserved
Website Feedback
Please use Feedback for website issues only. For all personal requests use the Contact page.
Purpose:
